{
    "id": "d8127aea4b0549a28f93bbcb15f46f07",
    "title": "Rewrite sentences as directed",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "2b2adae3c6e24362a222baec7ad08e83",
            "title": "Fill In The Blanks",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The tea was .................................. hot for me to drink.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "too"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is ................................... arrogant that he will not listen to advice.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "too"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He worked hard ...................................... the examination.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "passing",
                        "to pass"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is .................................... stupid that he cannot handle such a situation.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "very",
                        "too"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "John is taller ................................... any other boy in the class.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "than",
                        "then"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "..................................... trying, I could not do it.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "However",
                        "Despite",
                        "Although"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................... I heard the gunshot I rushed to the spot.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "As soon as",
                        "No sooner"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "No sooner had I solved one problem ................................... another cropped up.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "than",
                        "when",
                        "before"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................... trained graduates need to apply.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "None",
                        "None other than",
                        "None but"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................... you do not work hard, you will fail.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "If",
                        "Unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}